That place...
...belongs to me!
What?
No, no, no, no...
No, this isn't happening!
I didn't mean to do this!
Shuichi! Shuichi! Say something!
Shuichi! Shuichi! Please!
Shuichi, say something!
Shuichi! Shuichi!
You piece of shit!
Oh, Clair. It's you.
Hey... Why are you inside of Shuichi?
To... kill you.
How terrible. Your only sister...
Why...? Why did you kill Mom and Dad?
Don't you watch the news?
The police said it was an accident with the gas.
Why?!
I knew it'd be bad seeing you again.
I don't see why you had
to bring this up in front of Shuichi.
They were bad people.
They were always so strict with us.
"Get your act together,
our family has an image to uphold."
Dad was a legislator,
but he did bad things behind the scenes.
Mom had an affair with one of
the young employees at her company.
Even you said it:
"I'm going to kill them one day."
So I did it. For you.
I am no longer the weak sister you knew,
the one you had to protect.
I'm strong now.
From now on, I'll protect you.
Do you still have the coin I gave you?
I threw it away.
I'll give you another one, then.
Take it to the abandoned
motel along the highway.
Hello. It's me.
Okay. Yes.
Got it.
Sorry, Clair. Something came up.
Make good use of the coin, okay?
Seriously.
I'm sorry it ended this way, Shuichi.
But I'm going to keep my promise.
Nn...
No! Clair!
Don't die, Clair!
Shuichi...
You're alive?
Uh, I'm not sure that
this qualifies as "alive," but...
But you can't die too!
Your promise...!
You're so stupid!
You shouldn't be worried
about others when you're like this!
Clair! I can't brea--
"Hotel Mythos"
"Running Spirit"
Mmm?
Who are you?
Ooh, that looks like it hurts!
--Huh?
What happened to you?
Hold on!
Oh, come on!
You should have told me you had a coin!
Ok, let me see it.
Stay back!
Hang on, Clair. This guy knows about the coins.
Can you fix him?
I won't know until I take a look.
Clair...
Try anything funny, and you'll regret it.
Hmm...
No problem. I can fix him. He's still alive.
Well then, hand over the coin please.
This? I can't.
I need the coin to fix him.
You're sure you can fix Shuichi, huh?
Yes.
Here! Drink that.
What the hell is it?
It's a bit hard to explain...
Sort of controlling microbes
with molecular mechanisms...
Forget about the theory.
If he drinks it, his neck will reattach.
What'll you do, Shuichi?
Okay, I'll drink it.
What a relief, eh?
If you'd gone back to your normal form
in that state, you would have died!
So it's true!
All right, hold it down tight.
If you don't, it might stick on crooked.
Hey, is it okay if I get out?
Yes, that's fine.
Sorry, Shuichi. You mind?
Go ahead.
Oooh...
What?
Well, you just have a surprisingly lovely body.
You, too. You're pretty handsome, huh?
This body?
I've simply adopted the most
suitable one for fitting in on this planet.
We don't actually have static forms.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Oh? Haven't you heard?
I'm what you people call an alien.
--What?
--Huh?!
I totally thought someone
told you before you came!
You'll be sure to keep my personal
information private, won't you?
What are you looking at?!
Well, I am certainly an alien,
but physically speaking,
I'm a complete human male, so...
Excuse me, might I touch them just--
What are you doing?!
Oh, sorry! Reflex!
Please trust me! I'm not a bad alien!
Here! I'll demonstrate.
Your name is Clair, right?
Please give me one of
your hairs from down there.
Wha--?
They haven't started growing yet!
What?!
That's a lie.
A lie?!
I'm not giving a single hair off
my head to someone I don't know.
Okay, that's fine.
I'll just used the one
I snatched when you kicked me.
Question: Do you like yourself?
Or do you hate yourself?
That's a pointless question.
You don't get to choose who you are.
If you still can't find anything
at all to like about yourself...
You should just die.
I see. Some people wish they
were someone else, though, right?
I think it could happen to just about anyone.
Aside from people that are
really into themselves, I guess.
Don't you ever think...
...you'd like to turn into someone else?
You're not the slightest bit intrigued?
The prospect of becoming
the person you've wanted to be...
A greater version of your current self.
Your body really is quite nice.
I think I'll stick with it.
You're not the slightest bit intrigued?
A new and different version of you.
I can change your life in ways
that will surely be... interesting.
Just like your friend there.
Was he the one that made me this way?!
How did you change Shuichi into a monster?
With medicine. Similar to the one he just drank.
Still, calling him a monster is a little rude!
That was the form he desired--his ideal form!
The medicine works by changing
the body as its owner desires, you see.
You've got to be joking!
I never wanted to turn into this thing,
and I certainly don't
remember drinking that medicine!
I'm the one who made you take that form.
What an incredible idea!
Letting someone inside of you
to make up for your own weakness.
Humans really are more
imaginative than I thought.
It sounds like you're
the source of all this trouble.
I'll accept the fact that you're an alien...
...but I'd like you to drop that appearance.
You're freely revealing my...
personal information.
Oh, what a shame. I really liked this body.
It should be okay for you to transform back now.
Ah, Cla--
Hey, Clair... What is it?
We were on the way back to our home planet.
Physical forms become a nuisance
during long trips through space,
so we compressed our minds
and knowledge into data.
That's what those coins are.
However, our spaceship
wore down and eventually broke.
We ended up crashing here.
My brethren were flung
from the ship and spread out.
Repairing the ship and finding my friends
are outside of my realm of expertise,
so I'd like you to join the ranks of "gatherers"
that are looking for my friends.
Naturally, you'll be compensated.
We'll start with a single coin.
With it, I give you medicine
that lets you transform.
But that's not all...
If you collect 100 coins,
you can do something even more amazing!
What are you talking about?
Do you like comic books?
Comic books?
Cartoons or movies are good, too.
They're really entertaining, huh?
I've been hooked on them since I got here.
Isn't it amazing?
Turning into a giant and
defeating a whole city of enemies,
using your own energy to destroy
a planet--they can do anything!
Wouldn't it be cool if you could
turn into something like that?
Let me ask you another question.
What is it?
Shuichi. Have you ever
picked up one of those coins before?
No.
Shuichi has no memory
of how he became a monster.
Someone probably made him drink it
or something--you know about that?
Might involve a girl two years older
than me with communication problems.
Oh, is there really a
bad person like that out there?
Anyhow, whether or not
you participate is up to you.
The coin...
In exchange for power, you lose everything.
I see. I'll think about it.
Lucky I found these sandals!
You don't know my sister at all then, do you?
She's the same year in school as you,
but she's always gone to
private schools in other areas,
so it'll be hard to find out
what your connection is.
That bitch did it, though.
I don't know how,
but she took that medicine and--
--Clair, no!
--Huh?
You can't use the coin.
You have another, don't you?
Things keep getting worse.
I've almost been killed twice
in the past two weeks.
And you're unable to transform.
If this keeps up--
You're wrong.
What?!
Things are much better for me now.
Way better than before
my sister killed our parents.
Yeah... The worst of it was
just after my sister disappeared.
I told people what happened,
but nobody believed me.
There was no place for me in the world.
But that all changed when I met you.
My life seemed to start up again.
And I found a place in it for me.
It's really incredible!
There's an alien that gives you crazy powers,
plus my sister is all wrapped up in it!
I've never been so excited!
It's okay. I won't use the coin.
I've got you.
Clair and I are really are completely different.
Oh my god, that's so funny!
Huh?!
Hey, where the hell do you think you're going?
Why are you... so strong...?
Hey, Kagaya! What's going on?
Oh, Abukawa!
Hmm?
Hey, where are your glasses?
I switched to contacts.
Kagaya feels a bit different lately, huh?
What do you mean?
I guess he just seems more adult or something...
What's up, Mifune?
Huh? How did you...?
I saw you coming up the stairs a minute ago.
Oh...
I wanted to give your notebook back to you.
Oh.
One of the girls in our class was
saying how you're kind of cool now.
Your glasses weren't so bad, tho--
Mifune...
What would you do if
the world was going to end today?
Huh? Oh, is this one of those
"what would you take to
a deserted island" questions?
No.
What if there was someone
who didn't care about other people,
and that person became incredibly powerful...
So powerful that they could destroy
this town, or the entire planet.
The world could end out of nowhere.
With no warning.
If something like that could happen today...
Um... Well... I don't know,
that sounds tricky...
Well, I... I guess, for me,
I'd be worried about my parents,
and all my classmates...
I'd try to stop the bad guy
or do my best to make sure that didn't happen!
Yeah. That's normal, huh?
What?
Thank you. I needed to hear someone say that.
Later.
I'm just speculating,
but it's hard to imagine that
everything the alien said is true.
There's some big story lurking
in the shadows of this town.
And I'm pretty sure I'm not the main character.
But I won't run!
The spaceship went down
somewhere in those mountains.
There's a good chance we'll find some coins,
but also a good chance
we'll run into some enemies.
It's okay, Shuichi. You'll survive.
I'm with you.
Okay, let's go.
"Episode 5: Crazy Enemies"